It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
Positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's a family guy
There's Craig Hoffman. He's such a rebel.
Oh, my God, he is so gorgeous.
And he plays by no one's rules
but his own.
Meg, you should ask him out.
I mean, you're the only one of us
who's ever had a real boyfriend.
I'm back. I brought another picnic.
You're such a good listener.
You're not like the other boys.
You're so good with animals.
I guess I could give it a try.
All right, here goes.
Hi, Craig.
I was wondering if maybe you'd want to...
I don't know, go out sometime.
That's about as likely as me playing
by someone else's rules besides my own...
which I would never do.
I play by my own rules, nobody else's.
Not even my own.
- How about a movie?
- I don't go out with dudes.
- Mom, Dad, am I ugly?
- Of course not, sweetie.
Yeah, where'd you get
a stupid idea like that?
- Craig Hoffman.
- Craig Hoffman said that?
Well, he's a sharp kid. You might be ugly.
There, there, let me dry those tears.
Yes, your anguish sustains me.
Meg, honey, don't let
those awful kids at school...
make you feel bad about yourself.
I tell you what.
Tomorrow you and I are gonna go out
and get you some brand new outfits.
Maybe a pair of those low-rider jeans
that'll show off your cute butt, huh?
Really? Wow, thanks, Mom.
Meg in low-riders.
Enough of that.
Go away, damn you.
You're going to get it now.
Oh, my God!
Horace, what is this all about?
What the hell's it look like?
I'm putting the bar up for sale.
Please tell me
this is some kind of practical joke.
Like the kind I used to play when
I was an intern at the hospital.
I'm afraid I have some very bad news.
Your wife's gonna be a vegetable.
You'll have to bathe her, feed her
and care for her the rest of her life.
Oh, my God.
No, I'm just kidding. She's dead.
Ever since that mega-mall opened
across the street...
it's been taking away all my business.
They got 300 stores, 200 restaurants...
53 bars, and an indoor cattle ranch.
I go to Baskin-Robbins
every night and buy myself a little treat.
Now, how in the hell am I supposed
to compete with that?
You need to fix the place up.
Reinvent The Clam's image
and we'll help you.
That'll take forever.
Not if we do a 1980s
fixing-stuff-up montage.
Well, I think we made it worse.
Boy, I do not envy
whoever has to clean that mess up.
Brian, why don't you take Stewie
while Meg and I go clothes shopping?
You know, it's awfully dangerous for me to
be walking around the mall at my height.
- I say, let me get on your back.
- Oh, for God's sake.
Strong with the force, young Skywalker is.
- God, I don't believe this.
- That is why you fail.
What about this, Meg?
A pink baby tee that says "Little Slut?"
- That seems pretty hip.
- I don't know if that's really me, Mom.
Well, they've got one that says
"Porn Star"...
and another that says "Sperm Dumpster"
and they're all written in glitter.
All right. All right.
Give me "Sperm Dumpster. "
That's the spirit.
- You finding everything okay?
- Yes, thank you.
- You just let me know if you need any...
- How do these jeans look?
- $10.
- $5.
- $8 and I'll do it.
- Fine.
Help, I've escaped
from Kevin Spacey's basement!
Help me!
I am so outrageous. Give me the cash.
- Cold in here?
- Nope, just really small.
Face it, Mom.
No matter what I wear, I look ugly.
Meg, you're being... That's...
Let's try down here.
Coming up next, Joan Rivers speaks
to us from beyond the grave.
But first, let's go
to the Quahog Mega-Mall...
where Asian correspondent
Tricia Takanawa...
is handing out makeovers.
That's right, Tom.
Some lucky hideous woman
will be transformed...
by our makeover magicians
into someone of value to society.
Meg, that's it. You could get a makeover.
That'd be just the thing to boost
your confidence.
Miss Takanawa! Miss Takanawa!
Over here!
My daughter needs a makeover like
there's no freaking tomorrow.
It looks like we've got a winner, Tom.
- Face it, The Clam is doomed.
- Come on, guys, we can't give up now.
Peter, we've tried every theme
we could think of and everything's failed.
Especially that Coyote Ugly theme.
It's no use, this place is finished.
Quagmire, go get the "For Sale" sign.
Hey, Horace, what the hell's this?
It's a karaoke machine.
I never got around to installing it.
A karaoke machine?
Wait a minute, that's it.
We'll turn this place into a karaoke bar.
Oh, man, that's the best idea
since they faked the moon landing.
Okay, cut.
Neil Armstrong.
Wait a minute.
You're supposed to be on the moon.
I just saw it on TV.
There's a... tape delay.
And solar winds...
Peter, take a look at your daughter.
Oh, my God, Lois, I'm sorry.
It was 20 years ago.
- I'd never even heard the word "rubber"...
- Peter, this is Meg.
Oh.
I got a makeover, Dad. Don't I look great?
Meg, honey, I always thought
you were beautiful just the way you...
God, couldn't do that with a straight face.
Welcome to the family, sweetheart.
Chris, go burn all Meg's old pictures.
There's got
to be a morning after
We're moving closer to the shore
I know we'll be there by tomorrow
And we'll escape the darkness
We won't be searching anymore
Thank you very much.
I don't understand it.
This place should be jumping.
Well, we just need to kick it up a notch.
Horace, hit it.
Just a small town girl
Living in a lonely world
She took the midnight train
Going anywhere
Peter, don't make me do...
Just a city boy
Born and raised in South Detroit
He took the midnight train
Going anywhere
Oh, God, I love this song.
And I love it when amateurs
sing the lyrics.
But I hate baseball cards.
Some will win
Some will lose
Some were born to sing the blues
The movie never ends
It goes on and on
Hey, that's Journey. Kickass!
Howard!
That is Journey.
Streetlight people
Get some! Get some!
Guys, we were freaking electric.
Yeah, they loved us.
Gentlemen, this is a sign.
We are gonna start our own rock band.
Who's with me?
I'm in.
Looks like the guys are gonna
form a rock band.
Maybe they'll learn a little something.
Stick around, you just might learn
something, too.
You know, Peter, just because you guys
entertained a bunch of drunken idiots...
at a karaoke bar, doesn't mean
you have what it takes to form a band.
Brian, you're just ants at a picnic.
We're gonna be awesome.
Wait. What am I?
I'm ants at a picnic?
Is that what you just said?
I'm ants at a picnic? All right.
Just making sure.
Sorry I'm late, fellas.
Cool, Glenn. You look just like Tommy Lee.
Well, I figured it'd be appropriate
since I just found out I got hepatitis.
You know, maybe we should have
decided on outfits that matched.
Now we all look like a bunch of queers.
Fellas, it doesn't matter what you wear...
as long as you play kickass rock and roll
and do this with your tongue.
- Am I right, Gene?
- You got that right, Pete.
Oh, my. Hi, Gene.
I didn't know you were here.
All right. Keep it in your mouth, rock star.
- Great job getting hot, Meg.
- Gee, thanks.
- Hey, Meg.
- Hi, Craig.
Now that you're attractive,
how about we go out sometime?
Gosh, I'd love to.
Great, I'll pick you up whenever
I feel like it.
Hey, Meg. We noticed Craig Hoffman
just asked you out.
That makes you cool.
Wanna hang out with us?
- Sure.
- Hey, I'm here to pick you up.
Here we are, fellas. Our first major gig.
Peter, this is a house of corrections.
You gotta start somewhere, fellas.
That's how you evolve.
Like when the Tin Man found out
he was gay.
Look what happened by accident.
I hear there's a lot of buzz about this band.
Yeah, there was a pretty positive review
carved in Tony's ass.
All right, kids.
Now everyone stay together.
It's very important to your father...
that we're here for his band's
first performance.
The people who beat you are proud
to present, all the way from Quahog...
Fat, Horny, Black and Joe.
- Hello, Cleveland!
- Hello, Peter.
One, two, three, four...
Oh, my God, we don't know any songs.
- You suck!
- Get off the stage!
What do we do?
I know what I'm doing.
I'm getting out of here.
How about a funny story
about Lake Wobegone?
It was the day
of the tuna hot-dish jamboree...
Oh, no. Kids, your father's in trouble.
- I'm going up there.
- I'm coming, too, Mom.
Oh, my God.
The guy behind me braided my hair.
Chris, grab a guitar. Brian, take the drums.
Here, Stewie, play with this.
Mom, can we please just get out of here?
- Oh, my God.
- Who is she?
God, I could strangle her all night long.
Boy, that's not healthy, is it?
That that's the first place I go to?
Hit it!
Cloudy skies and rain clouds
Have come to stay
Windy nights and sad sights
Won't go away
But I wanna be without a care
Unicorns and butterflies everywhere
Gonna buy me a rainbow
Gonna wrap it up in a great big bow
The time is right
It's day, not night
Just open up your heart
It'll be all right
Gonna buy me a rainbow
Buy me a rainbow
You guys were great.
My name's Jimmy lovine.
And I'd like to make you
filthy rich rock stars.
Wow, you're the chairman of
Interscope Records.
- What're you doing in prison?
- I stomped a cat to death.
Listen, you guys got talent.
- Well, where do we sign?
- Right here, on Tony's butt cheek.
And initial here...
and here.
And date.
Oh, crap. Today's the seventeenth.
Gonna buy me a rainbow
Buy me a rainbow
- How was that, Dr. Ditty?
- Yo, that sounds smooth, y'all.
I just have a...
God, I'm so sorry. I keep doing that.
God, please forgive me.
I get that from my father.
He's from a different generation.
- It's...
- Whatever, man.
- We cool? We good?
- Yeah, we're cool. Fine.
Mr. Doctor? If you get shot in a rap feud...
can you perform surgery on yourself?
Well, no, Chris. My degree's in optometry.
All right, Dr. Ditty.
I got three choices for you
for the name of the band:
Peter Griffin Starship,
Peter Griffin and the Sunday Steppers...
or Testicular Sound Express.
I think the name is Meg.
- Me? Why?
- Yeah, why?
Let me explain something to you, all right?
We got to get her half-naked
and put her out front, center stage.
And that's gonna make y'all billionaires...
because America loves
hot, white jailbait ass.
Wait a minute.
That's the smartest thing I've ever heard...
anyone say about anything.
I'm not sure I'm comfortable with Meg
being exploited that way.
Shut up, Mom, it's not your decision.
I want to be exploited.
Meg, don't you talk to me like that.
Look, Lois, I love Meal Ticket
just as much as I love Chris and Stevie...
but business is business.
So, let's get this show on the road, huh?
Good. Now, I just need you to sign this.
Oh, God. Sorry.
Oh, my God. That is not me.
That's not who I am. I vote Democrat.
It will not happen again.
We cool? We good?
You...
You guys know I have no problem
with black people, right?
Yeah. Sure.
You did say you hated Crooklyn.
- Hey, Doc, you got a minute?
- What you want, dog?
Yeah, so, hey, check it out.
Stewie and I have been working
on some stuff of our own.
And we thought there might be a place
for us to sing on the next album.
Hey, cool. You're busy. No sweat.
Boy, Benson was a funny show.
- I'll talk to you later.
- Well, what did he say?
He said he'd think about it.
Okay, so where were we?
Okay.
I want to have intercourse
with you
Intercourse with you
Relations.
- Right?
- Yeah. No, great, that sounds good.
All right, groovy.
Now, is there a shorter word
for intercourse?
Lois, go grab me another bag of Skittles.
- Excuse me, young lady?
- Did I freaking stutter?
- I said more Skittles.
- All right. That is it, Meg.
You know, ever since you
got that makeover...
you've developed a terrible attitude.
And all the success with the family band
is only making it worse.
The family band?
You know, maybe you haven't noticed,
Lois, but I am the band.
- Right, Missus Wong?
- Yeah, she band. Old lady jealous.
Peter, we have to do something.
We're losing our daughter.
I'm worried about
what's happening to her.
Lois, this is the kind of thing...
that always resolves itself
if you just ignore it, all right?
What's more important is
we're living the sweet life.
This is even more fun than
when I performed at the White House.
Mr. President,
I present to you Peter Griffin.
Okay, listen up, everybody.
I got great news.
Meg, you and your family are gonna
perform on Saturday Night Live.
You mean I'm gonna get to meet
John Belushi and Gilda Radner...
and Phil Hartman, and Chris Farley,
and Horatio Sanz? Sweet!
Saturday Night Live.
I can't think of anything more exciting.
Oh, my God, a water fountain!
Meg, I'm Jimmy Fallon.
It's great to finally meet you. I'm hosting.
Why don't you come hang out
in my dressing room?
- What are you looking at?
- Nothing.
Come on, let's go.
Peter, I'm worried about Meg.
She's spiraling out of control.
I mean, what if she develops
a coke problem?
No Coke. Pepsi.
Come on, you set me up for that one.
Wow, Jimmy.
That was everything
Ladies Home Journal said it would be.
Awesome, great, thanks.
You know, there's something I...
There's something I gotta tell you.
Being with you just made me feel
so... Live from New York...
it's Saturday Night!
It's Saturday Night Live.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, that wasn't a very good
opening sketch, was it?
- A rare miss.
- I don't think that was a sketch, Peter.
Mom, Dad, he used me for comedy.
Wait a minute.
Are you telling me
that my daughter was deflowered...
in front of one-and-a-half times
the Mad TVaudience?
My poor baby.
My God, Lois, you were right.
Why the hell didn't I see it coming?
All right, stand aside.
It's about time I did my fatherly duty.
I said "duty," but no time
to laugh about it now.
Hey, everybody, it's great to be back.
So we got a great show tonight and...
Hey, Fallon, say goodnight, you bum.
And this is for laughing
and looking at the camera...
during every sketch you've ever been in.
Who do you think you are? Carol Burnett?
You think because she did it,
it's okay for you?
You haven't earned what she's earned,
buddy.
All right, now where's the guy
who slept with my daughter?
I'm so glad to be the real me again.
It's too much work being beautiful.
Not for me, but it's good
to have you back, pumpkin.
Well, I guess there's only
one thing left to do.
Listen, thanks, everybody.
I had a great time tonight.
I want to thank Jimmy Fallon
for being such a good sport.
Lois, Meg, Stewie, Brian, Chris,
the guys from the prison...
Counting Crows.
If I'm forgetting anybody, I'm sorry.
Goodnight, everybody!
Our thoughts are with you, Chevy!
From the world famous
Apollo Theater in Harlem...
it's show time at the...
What? I'm tired.
It has nothing to do with the fact
that it's a black show.
What? I can't be tired at 1:00
in the morning?
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru